Oh
Still no word from the captain. We've been out here all night. I'm falling asleep
Lu Guang! Lu Guang!
Hey, you and I still have some talking to do.
Unless you want me to finish what I started. It's your choice.
You said his name was Lu Guang, right?
Well, now I know who it was that locked me inside the dark room with you.
You were controlling Liu Min. What do you want? Who are you?
If you keep shouting like that, those cops outside are going to come in.
Not so good for this girl I'm possessing. She might just wind up in jail.
Let's hold out until 6 and then we can check in.
Dispatch to 0814.
Or we can answer dispatch.
0814. Copy.
Suspect attempted suicide while in custody and is en route to the hospital.
Bring your persons of interest in for questioning.
He's bleeding badly. I can't just stand here and do nothing.
If I can get the knife, then I can take this guy down and help Lu Guang.
Fine, you win. Now what do you want?
So we're finally getting somewhere, but we can't negotiate yet.
You see, this relationship lacks honesty.
And I need you to prove to me that I can trust you again.
How do I do that?
Tell the truth. What exactly is that power of yours?
I can't quite figure it out. Although I'm fairly certain about how you activate it.
You clap. Am I right?
I'll admit, I didn't see that little trap of yours coming.
However, I did see your hands right before you disappeared.
So, we've established how you can turn it on.
Now I would like you to fill in the rest of the gaps for me.
Go ahead. What kind of limits does it have? I'm just dying to find out.
You're not going to like what happens if you lie to me.
I teleport. I can go anywhere as long as I have a clear image of it in my mind.
But I need focus, otherwise I can't go as far.
So yeah, that's why I need a closed environment. So I could concentrate on fighting you.
I told you not to lie! Seems your first punishment wasn't enough to get you to stop cheating.
Maybe this time it'll sink in.
See, you can fool me, but she sees right through you.
Wait! No!
I can't believe it's been right in front of me.
You covered that dark room with photos. Cause you need them as well.
Using photos of my past victims was a clever move.
I assumed they were there to rile me up.
Teleporting with pictures? Talk about a convenient power!
I think I might take it. See what kind of trouble I can get into.
You can do that.
Calm down.
All that matters is getting that knife.
To disarm an opponent, you need to target their joints so you can take control of their ability to use their weapon.
See, when you grab the wrist, they can't move to attack.
But then, if you grab the arm, they can still move and hit you.
Let's practice. Come at me with the knife.
It's natural to move away from what you're afraid of.
But in a fight, this gives your opponent more range to attack.
So when conflict is unavoidable, you can't let fear control you.
The way to win is to face it head on.
Hey! Hello?
Hello?
That's enough fun for today.
So let's pick this up again later. My new friend.
Mr. Chung?
Mr. Lu?
Mr. Chung? Mr. Lu?
Hold on a second.
Mr. Chung, you need to come with us. We have some questions to ask you.
He's been stabbed.
Mr. Chung!
Call an ambulance now!
Drop the knife!
Don't move!
Put your hands where I can see them right now!
Dispatch, go ahead.
There's been a stabbing. We need an ambulance at Shop 188.
What's going on?
He has multiple wounds and situations.
Dr. Chung?
Mr. Chung?
Mr. Lu?
Huh?
Mr. Chung?
Mr. Lu?
MaleAN glyc就是神城!
Who has multiple wounds and severe blood loss.
Suspect is in custody...
Where's Lu?
Le Guong?
Mr. אח!
It's okay.
Stay calm.
Forget me!
Please, somebody save him!
No!
I know how it looks, but I swear… I didn't stab anyone! It was Emma's murderer! He controls people! He was possessing Liu Min!
So you say. But then why should I believe you? Why would I want to hurt Liu Guang?
But Liu Guang, he's family to me! Watch the bleeding. I need suction.
Clamps. Here. You're not listening! I saw him make him a jump! What were you doing there?
Look, kid. Wasting our time with these stories won't help you. There were three people there, and you were holding the knife.
From what we saw, it doesn't look like the girl did it. You're all that's left. Yet you're saying our culprit is someone you can't even prove exists!
Can I talk to Captain Xiao? I'm sure he'll believe me.
Alright. You can call him.
How could we have known? It wasn't even a minute. We rushed back in as soon as we saw what he was doing.
Hey, what's up? Who's that? We're waiting at the ER. I know! But how could he strangle himself in that short amount of time?
Charging paddles. Three. Two. Clear. Charging. Three. Two. Clear.
Clear.
There's one thing after another. Before I forget, did you inform his family?
Yeah, I took care of it. But…
It won't be long before the Metaverse takes off, right? So best remember me when it does. He owe me that much.
I make no promises. Your phone's going off.
Yes, hello? I've already told you. As long as he's still breathing, you do not call me!
Huh? What's wrong? Sounded bad.
No, it's my stupid son, Lyumin. I'll take care of it. Yeah, it's me.
Lyumin wound up in the hospital somehow. Can you check on him?
Possibly.
Fine.
If anything comes up, handle it. Make this go away no matter the price.
Let's hope it's that easy.
If that fool was half as good as his younger brother, he might be worth the trouble.
Speaking of, isn't Liu Xiao about to get back?
That's neither here nor there. Let's move on.
Hey, boss. Have a good swim?
You mean again. He's in the hospital. Find which one.
Ah, on it! I can smell the money already!
Here. I got you take-out.
Thank you.
Leave it when you're done. I'll clean up later.
Hold on! Do you know how Lu Guang is doing?
He didn't make it through. Sorry.
You blew up the noodles for too long. This isn't soup. It's just a sad lumpy broth.
Leave the bowl in the sink after you finish. I'll leave the dishes later.
Get me into trouble again. Come back here and sit down. Help me with this?
The wind messed it up. You've been messing with that all day. It's not getting better.
I know, you idiot. Don't put the camera there. It's too damp.
Why did you wash this? I already did it last night.
Moron. It's Xiao Nae's mail. Don't try and change the past, alright?
Wait a sec. I can go back and make sure none of this happens at all.
That's it. I just need a photo. Then I can save Lu Guang!
Shun Xiaoxie, you're free to go.
Captain Xiao said to pick you up.
So hey, did they fill you in on the whole situation?
There's still a lot to do. Relax while you can, okay?
Do me a favor. Answer that for me.
Hey, it's me. You coming home tonight? Our daughter's been missing her father.
I might not make it home. I'm still on a case.
Captain Tian is here to see you.
Huh? He is? Weird.
Please tell him I'm busy, and I'll call him later. Sorry, but I gotta go now. I'm driving. Be safe, okay?
Promise you'll get some sleep.
Done. Love you.
Love you.
I didn't know you had a kid. You don't seem like the type.
Well, I sort of have one.
When did you take this? It looks recent.
Oh, it's from when we got married. What?
Uh, nothing.
Time sure flies. I took that two years ago, and we still haven't had our ceremony.
Two years. That's more than enough time. I could go back and change everything.
The past and the future must remain untouched.
You should get on that. Here's your phone.
Uh, by the way, I picked you up a change of clothes.
Why don't I want you to see Liu Guang looking like that?
I appreciate it.
You look good.
Okay. Are you ready?
How in the world are you still alive?
Sorry to disappoint, idiot.
That all came out very wrong.
Just get out so I can sleep.
Captain, someone told me that Liu Guang was dead.
That was deliberate false info for Liu Guang's protection. Liu Min's the one who died. The bastard.
He strangled himself with his handcuffs during a break in his interrogation.
Charging paddles. Three. Two. Clear.
Charging. Three. Two. Clear.
In all my years as a doctor, I have never seen a case like this one.
We don't know how he did it, but Liu Min dislocated his cricoid cartilage.
Basically crushed his own trachea.
But Liu Guang's fine. So why did the officer still lie to me?
I'm not about to tell a suspect something that the boss wanted me to keep a secret.
Yeah, good call.
I didn't give you the details because you told me that you already knew.
Or I thought you did.
I asked you if you were filled in, remember?
How would I know that's what you meant?
Maybe try being a bit more direct next time.
That guy keeping secrets, but that was way too vague.
How are you?
Huh?
I know everything that happened.
And that I was the one who stabbed Liu Guang.
We went over it all. And we have a theory.
If this guy does have the power to control people, Liu Min didn't kill himself.
He was used in the same way Chao Ling was.
Wait, what? How'd this happen?
I don't care that he's dead. What happened to his belongings?
Don't they go to his family?
It's complicated. He's a suspect in a murder case.
All his things are evidence now.
I'll figure out something.
But no matter what, it won't be easy.
I don't care what you have to do!
I'm not paying for half measures, I'm paying for results!
Do not stop until his phone is in my hands!
This is all we've got now.
Can you check the recent photos?
See what you can learn with that power of yours.
Find something we couldn't.
Liu Guang, you're still healing. Be careful.
Yeah, don't push yourself.
Hey, that's Officer Chen's phone!
Chen Bean?
Damn it!
Hang on, I'm coming with you!
I'm coming with you!
Actually, it might be better if I stay.
Hey, Captain Xiao! Did you find him?
Not yet. It's like he vanished.
Shit. Did you notice anything strange when he picked you up?